<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Broderic Duncan</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Broderic Duncan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2022 😎</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RIP AirDrop</title>
      <link>/post/rip-airdrop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/rip-airdrop/</guid>
      <description>According to this article from CNBC, Apple will be changing how AirDrop works.
Originally, AirDrop had three options:
Receiving off Contacts Only Everyone Having the third option selected is pretty self explanatory, it allowed you to received messages from anyone.
But now they&amp;rsquo;re going to be changing that third option to &amp;ldquo;Everyone (For 10 Minutes)&amp;rdquo; This means that AirDrop will be enabled to receive messages from anyone for only 10 minutes at a time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Printing From My iPhone</title>
      <link>/post/printing-from-my-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/printing-from-my-iphone/</guid>
      <description>For the longest time I&amp;rsquo;ve never been able to print from my iPhone to the Dell printer in my parent&amp;rsquo;s house. I&amp;rsquo;m not exactly sure when we got the printer but I know it&amp;rsquo;s at least been like 7+ years. The printer in question is the Dell 2155cn Color MFP. According to the copyright on the user guide, the printer was released in 2010. That makes the printer a decade+ old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Networking My Parents&#39; House</title>
      <link>/post/networking-a-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/networking-a-house/</guid>
      <description>So before I began this project, it was clear that the network closet was a mess:
Wires and cables everywhere. The patch panel is unorganized. There&amp;rsquo;s so much crap everywhere you can&amp;rsquo;t even tell what&amp;rsquo;s going on. I do want to say that most of this was not me. This was the previous owner. When we moved into the house the previous owner had already wired every inch of it with cat5e and coaxial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Hugo</title>
      <link>/post/thoughts-on-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/thoughts-on-hugo/</guid>
      <description>I originally found out about Hugo after browsing Hacker News (YCombinator) and coming across a blog with a footer containing a link to Hugo&amp;rsquo;s site. You can scroll to the bottom to get an exact example of what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about. If you click on the link you can see Hugo advertised as: &amp;ldquo;One of the most popular open-source static site generators.&amp;rdquo; Beforehand, I had been thinking about creating my own site and was researching what exactly I wanted to build my site with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about-bak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-bak/</guid>
      <description>Hi I&amp;rsquo;m Broderic and I have no clue how to use computers.
I&amp;rsquo;m currently pursuing a degree in IT with a focus on cybersecurity. I created this site for a couple reasons. The first being for me to have somewhere to write about and publish whatever I find interesting. And the second being I want to document any projects I&amp;rsquo;m working on. Documentation is a huge part of IT and I don&amp;rsquo;t think it hurts to practice that skill every now and then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi I&amp;rsquo;m Broderic and I have no clue how to use computers.
I&amp;rsquo;m currently pursuing a degree in IT with a focus on cybersecurity. I created this site for a couple reasons. The first being for me to have somewhere to write about and publish whatever I find interesting. And the second being I want to document any projects I&amp;rsquo;m working on. Documentation is a huge part of IT and I don&amp;rsquo;t think it hurts to practice that skill every now and then.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
