<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Broderic Duncan</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Broderic Duncan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2022 😎</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Printing From My iPhone</title>
      <link>/post/printing-from-my-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/printing-from-my-iphone/</guid>
      <description>For the longest time I&amp;rsquo;ve never been able to print from my iPhone to the Dell printer in my parent&amp;rsquo;s house. I&amp;rsquo;m not exactly sure when we got the printer but I know it&amp;rsquo;s at least been like 7+ years. The printer in question is the Dell 2155cn Color MFP. According to the copyright on the user guide, the printer was released in 2010. That makes the printer a decade+ old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Hugo</title>
      <link>/post/thoughts-on-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/thoughts-on-hugo/</guid>
      <description>I originally found out about Hugo after browsing Hacker News (YCombinator) and coming across a blog with a footer containing a link to Hugo&amp;rsquo;s site. You can scroll to the bottom to get an exact example of what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about. If you click on the link you can see Hugo advertised as: &amp;ldquo;One of the most popular open-source static site generators.&amp;rdquo; Beforehand, I had been thinking about creating my own site and was researching what exactly I wanted to build my site with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/post/networking-a-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/networking-a-house/</guid>
      <description>title = &amp;ldquo;Networking My Parents&amp;rsquo; House&amp;rdquo; description = &amp;quot;&amp;quot; tags = [ &amp;ldquo;networking&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;unifi&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;ubiquiti&amp;rdquo;, ] date = &amp;ldquo;2022-06-01&amp;rdquo;
+++
So before I began this project, it was clear that the network closet was a mess:
Wires and cables everywhere. The patch panel is unorganized. There&amp;rsquo;s so much crap everywhere you can&amp;rsquo;t even tell what&amp;rsquo;s going on. I do want to say that most of this was not me. This was the previous owner.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
